准备好了吗  孩子们
Are you ready, kids?
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
我听不见
I can't hear you
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
是谁住在深海的大菠萝里
Who lives in a pineapple under the sea?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
方方黄黄伸缩自如
Absorbent and yellow and porous is he
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
如果四处探险是你的愿望
If nautical nonsense be something you wish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
那就敲敲甲板让大鱼开路
Then drop on the deck and flop like a fish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
准备
Ready
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
痛苦夜班
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
蟹堡王
啊  蟹堡王
Ah, The Krusty Krab
裤头村最顶级的日间餐厅
Bikini Bottom's premiere daytime eatery
开
关门时间差不多就
where it'll be closing time right
在
about
关
现在
now
八点了
8:00
永别了  傻蛋们
So long, suckers
我跟个小姐有一场热辣约会
I've got a hot date with a little lady
这小姐就叫做竖笛
and her name is Clarinet
干嘛
What?
你们还开门吗
Are you open?
看牌子
Read the sign
我要份豪华蟹黄堡还有双倍辣海草条
I'll have a Krabby Patty Deluxe
and a double chili kelp fries
想得美
No, you won't
我可不能一整晚都待这里
I can't hang out here all night
我还有好日子要过
l've got a life
你不要我钱就算了
Well, fine, if you don't want my money
钱
Money?
你意思是  要是我们等会还营业
You mean, if we stayed open later
你就会给我们钱吗
you'd give us your money?
对
Sure
章鱼哥先生  欢迎来到夜班
Mr. Squidward, welcome to the night shift
关
从现在起  蟹堡王每天24小时营业
From now on, The Krusty Krab is open 24 hours a day
什么
What?
现在我们再也不用下班了
Now we never have to stop working
蟹老板
Mr. Krabs
明早见  小子们
See you in the morning, boys
我可不能一整晚都待这里
I can't hang out here all night
我还有好日子要过
I got a life
蟹老板
Mr. Krabs
这不挺好的吗  章鱼哥
Isn't this great, Squidward?
就我跟你几小时几小时几小时在一起
Just you and me together for hours and hours and hours?
然后等到出太阳
And then the sun'll come up?
就是明天了  结果我们还在工作
And it'll be tomorrow, and we'll still be working
就跟睡衣派对一个样
It'll be just like a sleepover
只是我们会流满汗沾满油
Only we'll be sweaty and covered with grease
准备好摇滚了吗  章鱼哥
Are you ready to rock, Squidward?
没
No
行  因为有客人来了
Good, 'cause we've got customers
给
Here
打我打得越用力越好
Please hit me as hard as you can
章鱼哥
Squidward
我在厨房里干活
I'm working in the kitchen
晚上干的
At night
别犹豫  打下去
Don't hold back
章鱼哥  你猜怎么着
Hey, Squidward, guess what?
我在切生菜
I'm chopping lettuce
晚上切的
at night
快看  我在擦厕所
Look at me, I'm swabbing the bathroom
晚上擦的
at night
我烫到我手了
I burned my hand
晚上烫的
At night
晚上  晚上
Night, night
晚上
Night
给我消停一点
Will you, please?
给  出去倒垃圾让我安静会
Here, give me a moment's peace and take out the trash
好的
All right
出去倒垃圾
Taking out the trash
晚上倒
at n
是要我出去倒吗
You mean, outside?
对  垃圾桶就在外面
That's where the dumpster is, yes
不好吧  章鱼哥
l don't know, Squidward
外面有点黑
it's kind of dark out there
我还以为你喜欢夜班
But I thought you liked the night shift
说得对
You're right
为了蟹堡王
For The Krusty Krab
小菜一碟
Piece of cake
所以说你不害怕了
So, you're not afraid?
对
Nah
可我怕  特别是过了
Well, I am, especially after
那个  你懂的
well, you know
什么
What?
懂什么东西
What do I know?
不记得了吗
You don't remember?
到处都有报道的
It was all over the news
跟我说
Tell me
不行  我多半不该说
No, no, no, I-I probably shouldn't
你这夜班会上不下去的
lt would ruin the night shift for you
怎么了
What happened?
所以你从来就没听说过
You mean you've never heard the story of the
铲子杀人魔吗
"Hash-Slinging Slasher"?
伞子扒人摸
The Slash-Bringing Hasher?
铲子杀人魔
The Hash-slinging Slasher
懒子拉人
The Sash-Wringing
毯子撒人
the Trash-Singing
螨子罚人
Mash-Flinging
返子傻人
the Flash-Springing
拉人
Wringing
侃  侃子
the-the Crash
打人
Dinging
对  铲子杀人魔
Yes, the Hash-Slinging Slasher
但是
But
大多数人只管他叫铲啊
most people just call him the Ha
因为他们话音未落
because that's all they have time to say
就会被他
before he
抓住
gets them
跟我讲铲子杀人魔的事
Tell me the story
好几年以前  就在这家餐厅里
Years ago, at this very restaurant
铲子杀人魔曾经也是个煎炸厨师
the Hash-Slinging Slasher used to be a fry cook
就
just
像
like
你
you
不过比你笨手笨脚
Only clumsier
然后  一天晚上
And then one night
他在切肉饼的时候
when he was cutting the patties
事情发生了
it happened
他忘加秘制酱料了
He forgot the secret sauce?
没忘
No
他没有洗手
He didn't wash his hands?
有洗
No
没有切整齐
Irregular portions?
屁
No
他不小心把自己的手给切断了
He cut off his own hand by mistake
你说的是这样吗
You mean like this?
还是这样
Or like this?
这样吗
Or this?
那这样呢
But what about this?
这样呢
Or this?
反正他不是海绵
Except he wasn't a sponge
所以说
So?
所以说那手没有再生
So it didn't grow back
他用一把生锈铲子接到原先手的位置
And he replaced his hand with a rusty spatula
然后  他被公交车给撞了
And then he got hit by a bus
在他葬礼上
And at his funeral
他被开除了
they fired him
火 化
所以现在  每逢
So now, every
今天周几
what day is it?
周二
Tuesday
周二晚上  他的冤魂就会回到蟹堡王
Tuesday night, his ghost returns to The Krusty Krab
展开他可怕的复仇
to wreak his horrible vengeance
可今晚就是周二晚上
But tonight's Tuesday night
那他就要来了
Then he'll be coming
要怎么知道他来了
How will we know?
有三种迹象会表示
There are three signs that signal
铲子杀人魔要来了
the approach of the Hash-Slinging Slasher
第一个迹象  灯会闪来闪去
First, the lights will flicker on and off
第二
Next
这位  能来点番茄酱吗
Dude, can I have some ketchup?
给你
Here you go
第二个迹象
Next
电话响起来却无人应答
the phone will ring, and there will be nobody there
最后一个迹象  铲子杀人魔
And finally, the Hash-Slinging Slasher
坐着撞了他的公交车的灵魂到了这
arrives in the ghost of the bus that ran him over
然后他走下了车
Then he exits the bus
没看两边的车况就过了马路
and crosses the street without looking both ways
因为他早就死掉了
because he's already dead
然后他会用他的灰白铲子手敲窗户
Then, he taps on the window
with his grizzly spatula hand
不要
No
他打开门
He opens the door
慢慢
He slowly
靠近了
approaches the
柜台
counter
知道他接下来会干什么吧
And you know what he does next?
干什么
What?
你真想知道吗
You really want to know?
干什么
What?
你确定想知道吗
Are you sure you want to know?
他他  他干什么了
What, what, what does he do?
整到你了
He gets you
整到
he get
天啊
Oh, my
海绵宝宝  我
SpongeBob, I
海绵宝宝  我就
SpongeBob, I was
我就只
I was just
海绵宝宝  我是开玩笑的
SpongeBob, I was joking
怎么了
What?
都是假的  没一段真的
It's not true, none of it is true
真的假的
It's not?
当然假的
Of course not
才没有人会拿铲子当手使
Nobody has a spatula for a hand
全都是玩笑
It was all a joke
蟹堡王
永远营业
你说棒不棒  章鱼哥
lsn't this great, Squidward?
白天从来就没时间擦天花板
There's never time to wash the ceiling during the day
什么二十四小时营业
Open 24 hours a day
完全就一馊主意
What a stupid idea
凌晨三点钟谁还想吃什么蟹黄堡
Who wants a Krabby Patty at 3:00 in the morning?
老天爷啊  凌晨三点了
Oh, boy, 3:00 a.m.
倒看看这地方
Just look at this place
跟个鬼地方差不多
It's like a ghost town in here
好玩吧  海绵宝宝
Very funny, SpongeBob
怎么了
What?
灯会闪来闪去
"And the lights will flicker on and off"
就跟我讲的差不多  我都懂
just like the story, I get it
章鱼哥
Hey, Squidward
你不动开关是怎么做到的
how are you doing that without moving the switch?
不是我干的
I'm not doing it
肯定是蟹堡王的电路太垃圾了
It must be the stupid faulty wiring in here
建这地方就没考虑要二十四小时营业
This place isn't built to run 24 hours a day
搞什么
What, what?
喂
Hello?
太会演了  章鱼哥
Nice try, Squidward
咋就演了
Nice try, what?
电话铃响起来  却无人应答
"The phone will ring and there will be no one there"
真是笑死我了
You crack me up
海绵宝宝  不是我干的
SpongeBob, I'm not doing this
要冷静  要冷静
Calm down, calm down
刚刚怎么一回事
All right, what was it?
有
There was
灯
the lights
有电话
and the phone
墙壁渗出来绿色黏液
And the walls will ooze green slime
等下
Wait
这是正常现象
They always do that
第三个迹象是什么
But what was that third thing?
我都不知道公交车这么晚还在开
I didn't know the buses ran this late
早就停了
They don't
上面有人下来了
Well, they're dropping someone off
伞子拉人
That's the Sash-Wringing
返子撒人
The-the Flash-Singing
阀子
The Fash
耙人
P-Pinging
铲子杀人魔
The Hash-Slinging Slasher
你可终于明白了
At last, you understand
咱要完蛋了
we're doomed
不对  还没完蛋
No, that's not it
我只是好感动
I am just so touched
看到你历经千辛万苦
that you would go to the trouble
打扮成铲子杀人魔
to dress up as a ghostly fry cook
站到马路对面去
and stand on the other side of the street
只为逗我开心
just to entertain me
你肯定真心喜欢上我了
You must really like me
海绵宝宝  你的论断有两处问题
SpongeBob, there are two problems with your theory
第一  我讨厌你
One: I hate you
第二
And two:
我都站这了  那家伙怎么会是我
How can that be me, when I'm standing right here?
铲子杀人魔
The Hash-Slinging Slasher
他要翻了我
He's going to flip me
快走开  快走开
Get away, get away
海绵宝宝  不管我刚才说了什么
SpongeBob, no matter what I've said
我还是有点喜欢你的
I've always sort of liked you
章鱼哥  我用你竖笛疏通过我马桶
Squidward, I used your clarinet to unclog my toilet
快走开  快走开
Get away, get away
这边不欢迎你
You're not welcome here
我能申请一份工作吗
Can I have a job application?
我把我自个的铲子给带来了
I brought my own spatula
我先前打过电话  不过因为紧张挂了
I called earlier, but I hung up 'cause I was nervous
你有推荐信吗
Do you have references?
等下  如果打电话和在公交上的是你
Wait, if that was you on the phone and you on the bus
那到底是谁在弄灯
then who was flickering the lights?
诺斯费拉图
Nosferatu
蟹老板的恋爱
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
分镜
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
蟹堡王
一正针两反针
Stitch one, purl two
那什么味道
What's that smell?
收银机
The register?
四十九块
Forty-nine o
八分
Eight?
少了一分钱
That's a penny short
不好了
Oh, no
一分钱怎么没了
Not a penny
救命
Help
有谁来帮个忙
Somebody, help us
就一分钱而已  老板
It's just a penny, sir
没什么大不了的
It doesn't matter
这还没什么大不了吗
Doesn't matter?
有钱能使世界转  小子
It's money that makes the world go round, boy
有钱能使你裤子方
It's money that keeps your pants square
有钱能使章鱼哥用褶边香皂洗澡
It's money that keeps Squidward in frilly soap
丁香味
Lilac
有钱能使我们整修蟹堡王
It's money that paid for all them renovations we did
七大洋里钱是最重要的了
Nothing in all the seven seas could matter more
重要程度还要大过
Not even that
美丽动人的小可爱
scrumptious, curvy cutie
我看到她了  蟹老板
I see her, Mr. Krabs
加奶酪的蟹黄堡
A Krabby Patty with cheese
经典无比
The classic
不是蟹黄堡  小子
Not the sandwich, boy
是拿着蟹黄堡的那个小可爱
The curvy cutie holding the sandwich
是我的驾校教练  泡芙夫人
That's my driving teacher, Mrs. Puff
泡芙夫人
Mrs. Puff?
她结婚了
She's married
不对  蟹老板
Oh, no, Mr. Krabs
她单身
She's single
那她丈夫怎么了
Then what happened to Mr. Puff?
她不愿意提起这件事
She doesn't like to talk about it
我愿付出一切抱得美人归
What I wouldn't give to have a lass like that on me claw
有了
I know
要不我带你过去介绍介绍
Why don't I take you over and introduce you?
不行不行不行
No, no, no
我我我太老了  小子
I'm-I'm too old, boy
对爱太过古板
Too hard-shelled for love
并且我衣冠也不整
Besides, I ain't properly dressed
没事的  蟹老板
come on, Mr. Krabs
你挺漂亮的
You look great
你先待在这  我去暖个场
You wait here while I go break the ice
海绵宝宝  等下别去
SpongeBob, no, wait
我太紧张了
I'm too nervous
嗨  泡芙老师
Hi, Mrs. Puff
快踩刹车  海绵宝宝
Hit the brakes, SpongeBob
小心那棵树
Watch the tree
等等  泡芙老师
Wait, Mrs. Puff
没在开船
We're not driving
对不起  海绵宝宝
I'm sorry, SpongeBob
我没料到会在这看到你
I didn't expect to see you here
我就在这上班  泡芙老师
I work here, Mrs. Puff
要认识下我老板吗
Want to meet my boss?
那个  我没
Well, I'm not
坐好别动
Don't move
泡芙老师  我要向你介绍蟹
Mrs. Puff, I'd like to introduce you to Mr.
泡芙老师  我要向你介绍
Mrs. Puff, I'd like to introduce you
我的老板  蟹老板
to my boss, Mr. Krabs
你好
Hello
蟹老板  快问个好
Mr. Krabs, say hello
不对  蟹老板
No, no, Mr. Krabs
说个你好就行
Just say hello
或许改天再
Perhaps another time would be
不行
No
别走
Wait
他要跟你说句话
He's trying to tell you something
蟹老板
Mr. Krabs
我听不大懂
I don't understand
蟹老板应该说的是他想要
I think Mr. Krabs is saying that he'd like to
用耙子打你
hit you with a rake
老天爷啊
Goodness
错了
No
要猜你体重多少
Try to guess your weight
好你这
Well
错了  等下
No, wait
他要带你去
He wants to take you
约个会
on a date
真的吗  蟹老板
Is that true, Mr. Krabs?
你真的要带我去约个会吗
Do you want to take me on a date?
对
Aye
你意下如何
What do you say?
我意下如何
What do I say?
我觉得你说话还挺有特色  蟹老板
I say, you have a way with words, Mr. Krabs
宝刀未老
I still got it
准备好约会了吗  蟹老板
Ready for your date, Mr. Krabs?
约会的事情我都胸有成竹  小子
I'm always ready when it comes to dating, lad
口气清新剂
Breath spray?
有了
Check
幸运手帕
Lucky hanky?
有了
Check
生锈大锚
Giant rusty anchor?
锚
Anchor
还有锚
Anchor?
我找不到生锈大锚了
I can't find me giant rusty anchor
放轻松  蟹老板
Relax, Mr. Krabs
一小玩笑而已
Just a little joke
祝你跟那个谁好运
Good luck with you-know-who
那个谁是谁
Who's that?
泡芙老师
Mrs. Puff
对
Oh, yeah
那就祝我好运吧  小子
Well, wish me luck, lad
奢华
蟹老板
Oh, Mr. Krabs
这晚餐可真是太好了
This dinner has been so wonderful
珊瑚煮得恰到好处
The coral was cooked to perfection
我都不舍得再咬一口了
I don't think I could eat another bite
那可不见得  我的小捕虾船
I doubt that, my little shrimp boat
你太宠我了  蟹老板
You're spoiling me, Mr. Krabs
毕竟
I mean
有用餐间隙的足部按摩
foot rubs between courses
有漫画
Caricatures
还有进口的音乐
Imported music
为了你一切都好得不得了  小桃桃
Nothing's too good for you, my prickly peach
蟹老板  我想告诉你的是
What I'm trying to tell you, Mr. Krabs is
先生  你的豪华轿车到了
Sir, your fancy pantsy limousine is here
太好了
Wonderful
泡芙小可爱  你的车在等你了
Puffily-poo, your chariot awaits
那个
Well
你以后再也不用走路了  小围兜
You'll never have to walk again, my little lobster bib
好啊
Aye
您的账单  先生
Your bill, sir
搞什么
What?
账单
一百块钱
One hundred dollars
这玩意肯定是写错了
Well, this can't possibly be correct
抱歉  先生
My mistake, sir
感谢您指正
Thank you for pointing that out
这是您的账单
This is your bill
我都不太明白了  蟹老板
I don't understand, Mr. Krabs
你是怎么做到一夜花十万的
How can you spend $100,000 in one night?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
我就是忍不住要把钱全花她身上
I couldn't help but spend every cent I had on her
我就是控制不住自己
I couldn't control myself
那你要怎么办
What are you going to do?
不知道  小子
I don't know, boy
我明天还有一场约会
I've got another date tomorrow
夹在两个爱人之间害得我进退两难
I'm caught in the middle of me two great loves
可爱的泡芙老师  还有我剩下的钱
sweet Mrs. Puff and the rest of me money
真希望我能有什么办法帮忙
I wish there was some way l could help
可能还真有办法  小子
Perhaps there is, boy
我要让你来负责管理我的钱
I'm putting you in charge of me money
我不太明白  蟹老板
I don't get it, Mr. Krabs
你跟着我来约会
You come with me on the date
让我不要花钱
and don't let me spend any money
记好了  去公园可以便宜点
Now remember, we keep it cheap by going to the park
并且不管我向你要多少钱
And no matter how much I ask you
都不能把我钱给我
you don't give me any of me money
快给我一块钱
Now give me a dollar
不给
Nope
真乖
Good boy
你可以的
You'll do fine
是谁
Who is it?
是我  我可爱的小浮标
It's me, my beautiful bell buoy
等会就好
Just a minute
买花
Flowers
买花啊  小子
Flowers, boy
快买花去
Go get flowers
可你说过
But you said
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
不能空手见泡芙老师这样的时髦淑女
you can't call on a classy lady
like Mrs. Puff empty-handed
咱讲的不是这个
We ain't talking about this
也不是这个
or this
咱讲的是这个
We're talking about this
差不多要好了
Almost ready
赶紧的  小子
Hurry, boy
快去买花
get the flowers
泡芙老师
Mrs. Puff
你还是一如既往地漂亮
You're as beautiful as ever
真奇怪
That's funny
还以为我听到海绵宝宝说话了
I thought I heard SpongeBob's voice
确实
You did
他马上就会回来了
He'll be right back
今天他是我们的私人助理
He's our personal assistant for the day
不好意思
Excuse me
我得给我保险代理人打下电话
l have to call my insurance agent
当然可以了  我美丽的泡芙
Of course, my beautiful Puff
蟹老板
Mr. Krabs
我买了你要我买的花
I got the flowers you wanted me to buy
买什么了
What's that?
我给泡芙老师买了花
I got the flowers for Mrs. Puff
都已经说好了的  小子
We had an agreement, boy
你不应该把我钱给花掉的
You ain't supposed to spend any of me money
可你说
But you said
我来了
Here I come
给你的  泡芙老师
For you, Mrs. Puff
花
Flowers
真贴心
How thoughtful
这还有盒巧克力
And here's a box of chocolates
海绵宝宝  巧克力在哪
SpongeBob, where's the chocolates?
蟹老板  预算不够买
Mr. Krabs, the budget doesn't allow for
海绵宝宝  到泡芙老师家门口
SpongeBob, you can't go to Mrs. Puff's house
就一定得有巧克力
without chocolates
快去  快去
Hurry, hurry
巧克力
我把他们店里最大盒的买了
I bought the biggest box they had
买买买
Buy, buy, buy
花花花
Spend, spend, spend
就只会想到这点东西吗
Is that all you can think about?
尤金
Oh, Eugene
这是我给你买的巧克力
Here's those chocolates I bought for you
今天我们要干什么  泡芙老师
What are we doing today, Mrs. Puff?
吃饭
Dinner?
跳舞
Dancing?
还是去月球旅行
A trip to the moon?
蟹老板
Mr. Krabs
咱就只是去公园散步  记得吗
we're just going for a walk in the park, remember?
其实在公园散个步就挺好了
Actually, a walk in the park sounds perfect
今天天气不错
It's a beautiful day
我就只要戴个遮阳帽就
l'll just need to get a sun hat and
泡芙老师要遮阳帽  海绵宝宝
Mrs. Puff needs a sun hat, SpongeBob
她好像
I think she
太阳都晒到可怜的泡芙老师的头上了
The sun is beating down on poor Mrs. Puff's head
作为你的财务顾问  我建议
As your financial advisor, l suggest
没时间建议了
There's not time for suggestions
快去买帽子
Go buy a hat
可是
But
马上
Today
别担心  泡芙老师
Don't worry, Mrs. Puff
我会给你遮阳的
I'll shade you
海绵宝宝  快点
SpongeBob, hurry
遮阳帽来了
One shady hat
做得好  小子
Good job, lad
好吧
Well
谢了
thank you
可你真的没必要买
but you didn't need to buy one
我衣柜里已经有一顶了
I have a hat in the closet
没必要买
Didn't need to buy one
听见没  小子
You hear that, boy?
没必要买帽子
We didn't need to buy a hat
你不是该帮我省钱的吗
Aren't you supposed to be saving me money?
我尽力了  蟹老板
I'm trying, Mr. Krabs
可你一直在要我给泡芙老师买东西
but you keep telling me to buy things for Mrs. Puff
我整个都懵了
It's all really confusing
海绵宝宝  对不起
SpongeBob, I'm sorry
这都是我的错
This is my fault
我不太理智了
I'm not thinking clearly
我就此作出承诺  小子
I'm making a sailor's promise, boy
从现在起
From this moment on
我不会再叫你给泡芙老师买任何东西
I won't ask you to buy anything for Mrs. Puff
过了一会儿
海绵宝宝  泡芙老师需要新的毛大衣
SpongeBob, Mrs. Puff needs a new fur coat
你都要把我钱花光了
You're spending all me money
泡芙芙需要双新鞋
Puffy needs a new pair of shoes
你要把我搞破产了  小子
You're breaking me, boy
她需要上品珠宝
She needs fine jewelry
不要这么上品
Not that fine
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
海绵宝宝  你能来可真好
SpongeBob, I'm glad I caught you
我要你给泡芙老师买
I want you to buy Mrs. Puff
打住
Wait
我先来猜下
Don't tell me
你要我跑去店里
You want me to run down to the store
买泡芙老师根本就不需要的东西
and buy Mrs. Puff something she doesn't need
然后你要我再跑回来
Then you want me to run back here
这样你就能说  海绵宝宝
so you can say, "Aye, SpongeBob"
你要把我钱都花光了
You're spending all me money"
然后我就说
And then I'll say
可是蟹老板  我只是在照你说的做
"But Mr. Krabs, I'm only doing what you said"
然后你就说
Then you'll say
咱讲的不是这个  也不是这个
"We're not talking about this or this
咱讲的是这个
We're talking about this"
可是小子  这回不一样了
But lad, this time's different
泡芙老师需要这个
Mrs. Puff needs this
我们还去不去公园了
Are we going to the park soon?
拜托了小子
Please, lad?
算我求你了
I'm begging you
我可是只找到真爱的寂寞老螃蟹
I'm a lonely old crustacean who's found love
别让我把她失去了啊
Don't let me lose her
蟹老板  别
Mr. Krabs, don't
别哭了  蟹老板
Don't cry, Mr. Krabs
别这样了
Come on
没事  我马上去买总行了吧
Okay, I'm going to get it, see?
打起精神来  蟹老板
Cheer up, Mr. Krabs
你要的洗衣机来了
Here's that washing machine you wanted
打起精神
Cheer up?
我要怎么打起精神
How can I cheer up
你是要花光我辛辛苦苦赚的钱吗
when you're spending all me hard-earned cash?
看吧
See?
你刚刚又来了
You just did it again
你乱花别人钱  我就忍不住要说你
Lad, I can't help it
if you're loose with other people's money
该再给泡芙买烘干机配洗衣机用吗
Do you think Mrs. Puff will need a dryer
to go along with that?
蟹老板
Well, Mr. Krabs
想知道我在想什么吗
do you want to know what I think?
蟹老板
Mr. Krabs
钱包
Wallet
词典
乱花
Spend
蟹老板的钱包
Mr. Krabs' wallet
我都不知道海绵宝宝词汇量这么丰富
I didn't know SpongeBob had such a colorful vocabulary
其实我也有话要说  蟹老板
Actually, there's something I'd like to say, too, Mr. Krabs
恐怕我收这么多礼物会觉得不太舒服
I'm afraid I just don't feel comfortable
accepting all these gifts
还是各付各的吧
I'd rather go dutch
只要你不介意
If you don't mind
好吧
Okay
你可真是可爱  蟹老板
You're a very sweet man, Mr. Krabs